A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Transportation, 1977-1985
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1977-1985., Extent: 19 cu. ft. (19 boxes). (Box 1-19)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Lamberts Pt./Sewells Pt. Marine Terminals/Bond Prospectus/Trust Agreement, 1982. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Hamilton Property at Pinners Point, Purchase of, 1981. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Investigation, 1980. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Lease for the Operation of the Portsmouth Terminal, 1983. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Pinners Point Proposed Sale, 1979-1980. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Virignia Port Authority - newport News Marine Terminal/Notes Due City/Pier B Bond Prospectus, 1984. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Norfolk International Terminals, 1984. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Virignia Port Authority - Portsmouth Marine Terminal C: Notes due City/Capitalized Lease, 1975-1982. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Department of Beverage Control - General, 1981-1982. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - State Monopoly on Wine, 1983. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth's Attorneys Services and Training Council, 1982. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Department of Corrections - Community and Youth Services, 1982-1983. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Department of Corrections - General, 1982. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Department of Corrections - General, 1983. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Department of Corrections - Enterprises, 1983. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Department of Corrections - Davis Roger Trent, 1982-1983. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Department of Corrections - Community Diversion Incentive Act, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Department of Corrections - Employee Complaints, 1982-1983. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Department of Corrections - Executive Agreements 5 percent, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Department of Corrections - Executions: Coppola, Frank, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Department of Corrections - Fort Belvoir, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Department of Corrections - Good Time Laws, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Department of Corrections - Hickman Report, 1981 Sept 18. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Department of Corrections - Inmate Population, 1982-1983. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Department of Corrections - Insider Program, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Department of Corrections - Jails, 1983. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Department of Corrections - Juvenile Justice System, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Department of Corrections - Large Facility, 1983. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Department of Corrections - McBride, David Thomas, 1982. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Department of Corrections - Medical Care, Inmates, 1983. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Department of Corrections - Modules (Shock Probation), 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Department of Corrections - Allegheny County/MSI Corrections, 1982. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Department of Corrections - Augusta MSI, 1982. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Department of Corrections - Overcrowding: General, 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Department of Corrections - Scott, Wendell Oliver, 1983. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Department of Corrections - Sentence Reduction, 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Department of Corrections - Southwestern State Hospital, 1983. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Department of Corrections - Senate Joint Resolution 65 Task Force to Study Expansion of Printing and Data Processing Services, 1983. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Department of Corrections - Board of Corrections (Senate Bill 198), 1982. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Department of Corrections - Board of Corrections, 1981-1982. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Department of criminal Justice Services - General, 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Department of criminal Justice Services - General, 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Department of criminal Justice Services - General, 1982. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Department of criminal Justice Services - Delinquency Prevention Program Funding, 1982-1983. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Parole Board, 1983. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Parole Board - Senate Bill 105: Parole Board, 1982-1983. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Parole Board - Probation Study, 1983. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Parole Board - Parole Examiner, 1982-1983. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Parole Board - Corrections, 1982. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority - Elizabeth Brant School, 1983. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority - General, 1983. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Rehabilitative School Authority - General, 1982. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Department of State Police - General, 1983. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Department of State Police - Bureau of Criminal Investigations, 1982-1983. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Department of State Police - Emissions Inspections Program, 1982-1983. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Department of State Police - Motor Vehicle Inspections Program: Melfa Dispatch Eastern Shore, 1982-1983. (Box 19, Folder 5)